A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Israel, 1949-1972; 825; 9 box(es); 9 __Boxes
  - Israel - Medical Sciences, 825.A
    - Tel-Hashomer Government Hospital - Blood Groups, 1958-1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Tel-Hashomer Government Hospital - Blood Groups - Reprints, 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Israel - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 825.D
    - Atsmon, Yehoshuah (Sam de Groot), 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History, 1959-1969, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History, 1959-1969, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History, 1959-1969, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reports, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Hebrew University - Agricultural History - Reprints, 1960-1961, 1965-1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Hebrew University - Dovrat, Amos, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Hebrew University - Halevy, Abraham H., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Hebrew University - Henis, Yigal, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Hebrew University - Sive, Arye, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Journal of Mathematical Analysis, 1949-1952, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - National Physical Laboratory - Solar Energy, 1957-1966 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - National Physical Laboratory - Solar Energy, 1957-1966 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - National Physical Laboratory - Solar Energy, 1957-1966 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - National Physical Laboratory - Solar Energy - Reports and Reprints, 1955-1960, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Rehovat Agricultural Research Station - Irrigation, 1957-1963 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Shainberg, Isaac, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Weizmann Institute - Atsmon, Dan, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Israel - Humanities and Arts, 825.R
    - Hebrew University - American Studies, 1952-1955 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Hebrew University - Asian Studies, 1960-1964 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Hebrew University - Koebner, Richard, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Hebrew University - Koebner, Richard, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Hebrew University - Koebner, Richard - Reprints, 1951-1953 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Hebrew University - Near Eastern Studies, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Hebrew University - Near Eastern Studies, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Hebrew University - Near Eastern Studies, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Hebrew University - Near Eastern Studies, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Hebrew University - Near Eastern Studies - Reports and Reprints, 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Hebrew University - Senator, David W., 1952-1954 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Hebrew University - Wormann, Curt, 1950-1952, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Hebrew University - Wormann, Curt, 1950-1952, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Israel - Social Sciences, 825.S
    - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N., 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N., 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N., 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N., 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N., 1959-1972 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1962-1963, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Hebrew University - Eisenstadt, Samuel N. - Reports and Reprints, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Hebrew University - Gazit, Mordechai, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Hebrew University - Gazit, Mordechai - Supplementary Material, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Hebrew University - Landau, Jacob, 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Hebrew University - Talmon, Jacob L., 1953-1954, 1959-1965 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Hebrew University - Tradition and Change conference, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Hebrew University - Tradition and Change conference, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Israel - Virus Studies, 825.V
    - Hebrew University, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Hebrew University, 1960-1965 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Israel Foundations Trustees - Virus Studies, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Israel Foundations Trustees - Virus Studies, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - Israel Foundations Trustees - Virus Studies, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 79)
    - Israel Foundations Trustees - Virus Studies, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Israel Foundations Trustees - Virus Studies, 1953-1962 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Lebanon, 1946-1969; 833; 3 box(es)
  Five subseries as follows: 833 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 833 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 833 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 833 R Humanities and arts 833 S Social sciences
  - American University of Beirut - Public Health, 1956-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Syrian University - Books, 1951-1952, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Syrian University - Books, 1951-1952, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 833.A
    - American University of Beirut - Cardiology - Tabbara, Riad A., 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - American University of Beirut - Fuleihan, Farid Joseph David, 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - American University of Beirut - Giaccai, Leonardo, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - American University of Beirut - Histology, 1951-1952, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American University of Beirut - Histology - Kurban, Amal K., 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - American University of Beirut - Idriss, Hassan Misbah, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American University of Beirut - Neurophysiology, 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American University of Beirut - Tabbara, Riad, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lebanon - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 833.D
    - Agricultural Research Institute - Haraoui, Joseph, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American University of Beirut - Mathematics and Astronomy, 1950-1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American University of Beirut - Pipkin, Sarah B., 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - American University of Beirut - Study Grant, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lebanon - Humanities and Arts, 833.R
    - American University of Beirut - Arabic Translations, 1952-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - American University of Beirut - Frayha, Anis, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - American University of Beirut - Fuleihan, Farid A., 1957-1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - American University of Beirut - Hanania, Farid S., 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - American University of Beirut - Karal, Enver Zia, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - American University of Beirut - Kurani, Habib, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - American University of Beirut - Mahmassani, Subhi, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - American University of Beirut - Sarruf, Faud, 1956-1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - American University of Beirut - Watson, Curtis B., 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - American University of Beirut - Zurayk, Constantine K., 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - El Adib (Arab Magazine) - Moussa, Salama, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - French Archaeological Institute - Artifact Classification, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - French Archaeological Institute - Artifact Classification, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Islamic Maqassed Association, 1960, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Lebanese Conservatory of Music, 1953-1956, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Najm, Mohammed Yousef, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Syrian University - Islamic Studies, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Lebanon - Social Sciences, 833.S
    - American University of Beirut - Economic Research Institute, 1954, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - American University of Beirut - Economic Research Institute, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - American University of Beirut - Economic Research Institute, 1958-1961 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - American University of Beirut - International Relations, 1959, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - American University of Beirut - International Relations, 1959, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - American University of Beirut - International Relations, 1959, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Foreign Affairs - Books, 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 39)